Guide to the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Teaching Fellows Program files, 1975-2015; Accession 2016-A-072
  - English Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Epidemiology Public Health Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Film Studies Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - French Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Forestry Environmental Studies Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Germanic Languages Literatures Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - History Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - History of Art Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - History of Science Medicine Program Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Humanities Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Immunobiology Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - International Affairs Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Italian Language and Literature Appointments, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Linguistics Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - MacMillan Center Southeast Asia Studies Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Management Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Mathematics Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Molecular, Cellular Development Biology Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Music Departments Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Near Eastern Languages Civilizations Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Pharmacology, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Philosophy Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Physics Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Political Science Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Psychology Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Religious Studies Divinity School Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Residential College Seminar Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Sociology Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Slavic Languages Literatures Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Spanish and Portuguese Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Statistics Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Theater Studies Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - Women's Gender Sexuality Studies Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - Yale College Dean's Office Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - Applied Mathematics, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Economics, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 81)
  - Environmental Engineering, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 82)
  - Environmental Studies, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - Ethics, Politics, Economics, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 84)
  - Film Studies, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - French, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 86)
  - Geology Geophysics, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 87)
  - History, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 88)
  - History of Art, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 89)
  - History of Science Medicine, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 90)
  - Humanities, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 91)
  - International Relations, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 92)
  - Linguistics, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 93)
  - Mathematics, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 94)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 95)
  - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 96)
  - Mollecular, Cellular Developmental Biology, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 97)
  - Music, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 98)
  - Near Eastern Languages Literatures, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 99)
  - Operations Research, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 100)
  - Philosophy, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 101)
  - Physics, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 102)
  - Political Science, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 103)
  - Psychology, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 104)
  - Religious Studies Divinity School, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 105)
  - Slavic Languages Literatures, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 106)
  - Sociology, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 107)
  - Spanish Portuguese, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 108)
  - Statistics, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 109)
  - Women's Gender Sexuality Studies, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 110)
  - Perspective on Science Graders, 2005-2006 (Box 16, Folder 111)
  - Residential College Math Science Tutors, 2005-2006 (Box 16, Folder 112)
  - L C, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 113)
  - Course Assistants, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 114)
  - African Studies, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 115)
  - Council on African Studies, 2007-2008 (Box 16, Folder 116)
  - African Languages, 1996-2004 (Box 16, Folder 117)
  - TFP African Studies, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 118)
  - Accounting, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 119)
  - TFP Evaluations Architecture, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 120)
  - Cell Biology, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 121)
  - TFP BBS Danielle Waterbury, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 122)
  - Cognitive Science, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Devane, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Divinity School, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - East, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - EPE, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - EPH, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - EVST, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - F, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Genetics, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Hindi, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Humanities, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - IR, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Languages, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Residential College Seminar, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Senior Projects TF, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Special Program in the Humanities, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Study of the City, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - HNDI, 2007-2008 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - YCIAS -Hindi Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - YCIAS Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - YCIAS, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - African American Studies, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - AFAM, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - AFAM Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - AFAM Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - African American St., 2001-2004 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - American Studies, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - AMST, 2007-2008 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - AMST Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - AMST Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - TFP American Studies, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Anthropology, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - ANTH, 2007-2008 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - ANTH Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - ANTH Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Anthropology, 2001-2005 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Applied Physics, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Applied Physics, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - APHY Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - APHY Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Applied Physics, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Astronomy, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Astronomy, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - ASTR Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - ASTR Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Astronomy, 2000-2004 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - BENG Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - BENG Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 2000-2004 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Cellular Molecular Physiology, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Chemical Engineering, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - CENG, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - CENG Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - CENG Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Chemical Engineering, 2000-2004 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Chemistry, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Chemistry, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - CHEM Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - CHEM Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Chemistry, 2002-2005 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Classics, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Classics, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - CLSS Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - CLSS Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Classics, 2003-2005 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - College Seminar, 2003-2005 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Comparative Literature, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - Comp Lit, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - CPLT Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - CPLT Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - Comparative Literature, 2000-2004 (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Computational Biology Bioinformatics, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - Computational Biology Bioinformatics Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - Computational Biology Bioinformatics Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - Computer Science, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - Computer Science, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - CPSC Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - CPSC Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - Computer Science, 2001-2005 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Divinity School, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Divinity, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - East Asian Lang Lit., 2008-2009 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - EALL, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - EALL Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - EALL Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - East Asian Lang. Lit., 2001-2005 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Ecology Environmental Biology, 2008-2009 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Ecology Evolutionary Biology, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - E, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - E, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Ecology Evolutionary Biology, 2001-2005 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Economics, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - ECON Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - ECON Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Economics, 2001-2005 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Electrical Engineering, 2008-2009 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - ELEC Engineering, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - EENG Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - EENG Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Electrical Engineering, 2001-2004 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Engineering Applied Science, 2008-2009 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Engineering, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - ENAS Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - ENAS Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Council of Engineering (1 of 2), 2003-2005 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Council of Engineering (2 of 2), 2003-2005 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - English, 2008-2009 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - English, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - ENGL Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - ENGL Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - English, 2001-2004 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Daily Themes, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Environmental Engineering, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Environmental Engineering Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - ERM Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - ERM, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - EPE Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Film Studies, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - FILM Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - FILM Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Film Studies, 2001-2005 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - French, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - FREN Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - FREN Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - French, 2001-2005 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Geology, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - GEOL Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - GEOL Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Geology, 2000-2005 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - German, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - GMAN Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - GMAN Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - German, 2001-2004 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - History, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - HIST Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - HIST Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - History (1 of 2), 2001-2005 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - History (2 of 2), 2001-2005 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - History Previous Years, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - History of Art, 2006-2008 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - HSAR Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - HSAR Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - History of Art, 2001-2005 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - HSHM, 2007-2008 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - HSHM Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - HSHM Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Hstry Med Science, 2002-2005 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Humanities, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - International Studies, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - International Relations, 2006-2007 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - INTS Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - INTS Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - International St, 1999-2005 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Italian, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - ITAL Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - ITAL Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Italian, 2001-2005 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - LAST Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Linguistics, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - LING Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - LING Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Linguistics, 2000-2005 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Mathematics, 2007-2008 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - MATH Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - MATH Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Mathematics, 2000-2005 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - MB, 2006-2007 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - MB, 2005-2006 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - MB, 2000-2005 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - GSPS Appointments Spring A-G, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - GSPS Appointments Spring H-M, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - GSPS Appointments Spring N-Z, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Non-GSPS Spring Teaching Appointments (A-M), 2005 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Non-GSPS Spring Teaching Appointments (N-Z), 2005 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Non-GSPS Appointments Fall A-G, 2005-2006 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Non-GSPS Appointments Fall H-M, 2005-2006 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Non-GSPS Appts Spring A-M, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Non-GSPS Appts Spring N-Z, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Non-GSPS Appointments Fall N-Z`, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - UCG Fall, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - UCG Fall, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Non-GSPS, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Non-GSPS H-M, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Non-GSPS N-Z, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Immunobiology (MCDB) Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - MCDB, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - MCDB Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - MCDB Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - MCDB, 2001-2005 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Mech Engineering, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - MENG Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - MENG Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 2001-2004 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Music, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - MUSI Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - MUSI Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Music, 2001-2005 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - NELC, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - NELC Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - NELC Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Near Eastern L C, 2001-2005 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - OPRS Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - OPRS Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Operations Research, 2001-2005 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Philosophy, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - PHIL Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - PHIL Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Philosophy, 2002-2005 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Physics, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Physics Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - PHYS Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Physics, 2001-2005 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Political Science, 2007-2008 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - PLSC Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - PLSC Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Political Science, 2001-2005 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Political Science, 2001-2005 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Psychology, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - PSYC Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - PSYC Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Psychology (1 of 2), 2001-2005 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Psychology (2 of 2), 2001-2005 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Religious Studies Divinity, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - RLST Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - RLST Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Religious Studies, 2001-2005 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Slavic, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - SLAV Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - SLAV Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Slavic, 2001-2004 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Sociology, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - SOCY Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - SOCY Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Sociology, 2001-2005 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Southeast Asian Studies Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - SPPR, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - SPPR Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - SPPR Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Spanish, 2001-2005 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Special Programs in the Humanities, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Statistics, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - STAT Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - STAT Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Statistics, 2000-2005 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Theater Studies, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - THST Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - THST Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Theater Studies, 2001-2005 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Women Gender Sexuality Studies, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - WGST Allocations, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - WGST Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Women's Studies, 2001-2005 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Contingency, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Contingency, 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Contingency, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Contingency, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Contingency, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Contingency, 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Contingency, 2006-2008 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Majors Committee, 2000-2002 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Majors Committee, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Majors Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Majors Committee, 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Majors Committee, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Majors Committee, 2005-2006 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Majors Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Majors Committee, 2008-2009 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Course of Study Committee, 1999-2004 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Course of Study Committee, 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Course of Study Committee, 2005-2006 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Course of Study Committee, 2006-2007 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Course of Study Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Course of Study Committee, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Administrative files, 1967-2014; 1986-2014; Accession 2016-A-073
  Restricted until January 1, 2050
  - Dean's Annual Report, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dean's Meeting; Standing Meeting, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dental Insurance, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dining Halls, 1991-2005 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dissertation Fellowships, 1998-2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dissertations, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dissertation Submission, 1998-2006 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - ODEO Programs, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - IMSD Grant Proposal, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Diversity, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Diversity, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Office of Diversity, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Diversity Office, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Diversity, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Diversity, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Diversity - Toyota, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Women's Faculty Forum, 2003 December 13 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Meeting Notes, 2005 December 15 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Drug Policy, 1990-2007 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - University Drug Prevention, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Economic Growth Center Department of Economics, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - EPC, 2001 June 8 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Elizabethan Club, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Employment Data for Harvard University, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Employment Performance and Development Plan, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Yale/AARHUS University Exchange Agreement, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Exchange Agreement - Organization of American States, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Exchange Agreement - University of Sussex, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Exchange Agreement - Università Commerciale Luigi Bocconi, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Exec. Committee, 2004 January-March (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Executive Committee, 2003 October-December (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Exec. Committee, 2003 April-June (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Conacyt, 1992-2002 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - China Scholarship Council/Yale World Scholars Exchange Agreement, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence - Chile; Universidad de los Andes, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Royal Holloway and Bedford New College, Univ. of London Exchange Agreement, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Yale/Geneva, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Gakushuin University, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - King's College, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Exchange Programs, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - University of Monterrey, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Folger Insitutute, 1994-2005 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Faculty Mentoring Awards, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Faculty Mentoring, 2005-2004 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Faculty Mentoring, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Faith Hills, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Federal Issues, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Federal Issues, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Fellowships, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Fellowships, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Harriett G. Jenkins Postdoc Fellowship Program (JPFP), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Bouchet Fellowship, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Chan Fellowship, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - DAAD, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Danforth Fellowships, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Dissertation Fellowships, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Enders JMP Analyses Summer, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Endowed Fellowship, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - English Speaking Union (ESU), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Fan Fellowship, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Fan Fellowship, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Fan Fellowship, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Fan Fellowship, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Fan Fellowship, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Franke Fellows, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Gignilliat Fellowship, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Gignilliat Fellowship, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Gignilliat, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Gillian Fellowship, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Gruber Foundation, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Guggenheim Fellowship, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Grace Murray Hopper Graduate Fellowship, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Hanscom Fellowship, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Keller Fellowship, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Kwoks Fellowship, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Leylan Fellowship, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Light Fellowship, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - LUCE PRGH. Fellowship, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Mellon Fellowship, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Renovation Architects, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Soros Fellowship, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Association of Chinese Students and Scholars at Yale (ACSSY), 1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - AGS Reps, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Assesments, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Committee on Athletics, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Yale University Auditing, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Yale University Auxiliary, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)